Contact

aadit.k12@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/aaditkamat (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Object-Oriented Programming (OOP)

Java

Microsoft Office

Languages

English (Full Professional)
Hindi (Native or Bilingual)
Marathi (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

Dr APJ Abdul Kalam GIIS Award for Academic Proficiency (Class 12) Dr APJ Abdul Kalam GIIS Award for

Academic Proficiency (Class 9)

Aadit Kamat

Software Engineer Intern at Learnseeker

Summary

I'm currently an undergraduate student majoring in Computer Science at the School of Computing, National University of Singapore. As a college student, I delight in the fact that I have thus far been exposed to different tools and technologies and gotten the opportunity to step out of my comfort zone. I hope to extend the learning journey beyond what the school has to offer and believe that a great platform to do this is through internships. That is why I am open to job opportunities and involving myself in new experiences.

Experience

Learnseeker Software Engineer Intern December 2018 - Present NUS Furnace, Singapore

- Restructured the form in the main website to handle user inputs differently
- Used amatch's Natural Language Processing (NLP) capabilities to parse free form text input

from users and separate them into respective subject and level inputs for the backend

 Implemented a basic SMS Dashboard with a line chart rendered for an Active Admin page for

visual data analysis

- Added Data Tables for Marketing Dashboard
- Created new filters for an Internal Content Resource Management (CRM) software

built with Ruby on Rails

• Used Ruby on Rails' Active Record framework to make database manipulations

Singapore Civil Defence Force
Full Time National Serviceman
May 2015 - May 2017 (2 years 1 month)
National Service Training Institute (NSTI)

- Handled enlistment of NSFs into the force
- Streamlined administrative processes for recruits adjust to way of life and culture in a disciplined organisation
- Organised cohesion events for colleagues within NSTI
- Managed a team of 13 NSFs conducting internal administrative audits and supporting events such as recruit's Passing Out Parade & NSF Promotion Ceremonies in the role of a Non Commissioned Officer (NCO)

Education

National University of Singapore Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2017 - 2021)

Global Indian International School

CBSE AISSCE, PCM with Computer Science · (2008 - 2015)